Ednguyen92@gmail.com

EDWARD NGUYEN

OBJECTIVE

To pursue a part-time that would challenge my knowledge and experiences in a growing and successful organization. With my two years of progressive experience in customer service, in both retail and professional settings, I have a strong desire to express my excellent problem solving, strong customer relations, management, and administrative skills by pursuing a career that would lead to a challenging and successful position. My personal experience with managing staff, building strong relationships, and efficiency in a fast-paced environment will allow me to go above and beyond in my career path.

DESIRED SKILLS

I have excellent verbal, written, communication, and organizational skills. I am able to maintain confidentiality, able to resolve time-sensitive issues, and ability to learn quickly. I am dedicating to my work. I have experiences working with diverse ethnic cultural groups, and bi-cultural. I am best known and described by my previous employers as hard working and good at working under minimal supervision with strong work ethic. I am a conscientious, hardworking, out-going, multi-tasking, and self-motivated person. I am an independent self-starter. I am enthusiastic about my chosen profession and will go above and beyond what is required. I bring with me the following assets that I believe could enhance your practice:

- People person; People skills; excellent communication skills.
- Great Customer Services and Customer Relations.
- Excellent marketing skills
- Can type more than 65-72 wpm.
- Customer Service Oriented and able to pay attention to detail with speed and accuracy.
- Honesty, straightforward and consistently with detail oriented always making sure the tasks correctly and properly.
- Ability to effectively interact and communicate with clients, customers, vendors, coworkers, and the public.
- Demonstrating the ability to function effectively under different circumstances while maintaining a clear perspective of goals to be accomplished.
- Excellent interpersonal, oral and written communication and problem solving skills.
- Ability to speak, read, and writes two languages: Vietnamese and English
- Able to work effectively under pressure in a fast pace environment; patience and willing to interact and communicate
- Listen to determine needs of customers/vendors before offering a solution. Quickly establish rapport with customers/clients/vendors.

- Honesty, straightforward and consistently with detail oriented always making sure the tasks correctly and properly.
- Quick learner, self-starter, motivator, and strong team player.
- Excellent Outreach/Referral skill.
- Great performance in operating in a multi-tasking environment.
- Great accounting skills and understanding of payroll procedure.
- Great computer skills Experienced in entering data into the computer. Computer proficiency Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, and much more software.

EXPERIENCE

Google Shopping Express By 1-800 Courier

Delivery Operator

August 2014-Current (6 Months)

- Transport goods with special handling requirements.
- Communicate effectively with customers, vendors, and other team members.
- Perform work activates requiring cooperation and instruction.
- Function in a fast-paced environment and meet deadlines
- Work with minimal supervision

Google Shopping Express By Adecco

Store Operator

November 2013 – August 2014 (10 Months)

Reason for leaving: Job Position Change

- Execute daily shopping task and inventory.
- Validation Checks.
- Work closely with Store Managers, Employees, and Customers.
- Test new operational processes and provide key insights and quality feedback.
- Work with Google design team to test new operational processes and provide key insights and quality feedback.
- Outstanding customer relations, internet, and phone etiquette
- Attention to detail
- Ability to maintain accurate lists and error proof documents
- Interacts with Store manager, employees, and customers in a professional, efficient, and quality-focused manner.
- And other duties as assigned.

Michael's

Replenishment

2011 - 2012 (1 Year)

Reason for leaving: School

- Assist customers with choices by providing them with information about products
- Carry out re-merchandising, display, price markdowns duties
- Respond quickly and resourcefully to customer requests or concerns
- Organize the display of merchandise
- Represent the store in a professional and positive manner.

ImPark

Parking and Transportation

April 2015 – Present (3 year)

- Provide exceptional and outstanding service to all Guests and make them feel welcome.
- Cooperate with the hotel staff manager on guest service and posting issues.
- Communicate with hotel staff Manager on Duty (M.O.D.), or property manager regarding incidents.
- Make sure all cashiering is performed accurately and in a timely manner.
- Handle all emergencies using your best judgment at the time. Advise the hotel or property manager and your assistants afterward.
- Write daily shift summary in Log Book. This summary will include but is not limited to:
 - 1. Shift revenue.
 - 2. Issues and concerns involving customers, guests, employees, and the Hospital.
 - 3. Useful information on your shift (changes in forecasts, scheduling, etc.)

EDUCATION MILPITAS HIGH SCHOOL

Focus: General Education **Four Years Completed DE ANZA COLLEGE** Major: Computer Science

In Progress

SKILLS Computer Skills:

Microsoft XP, Vista, 7. Office: Excel, Publisher, PowerPoint, Word, Introductory C++
Mac OSX, Adobe Photoshop, Image Ready,

Interpersonal Skills:

Innovative, Team Player, Determined, Sociably Friendly, Punctual, Creative, Trustworthy, Dependable, Gets along and works well with others.

Additional Training:

Data Entry, Human resources, Business, Customer Service, Inventory, Bookkeeping, Stocking, Shipping, Sales, Advertising, Cashier.